

# PAVITHRA V

UI Designer & UI Developer

# **PROFILE**

I am highly skilled UI Designer and Front-end Developer with 2 years of experience in designing and developing visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces for web and mobile applications. Strong ability to code front-end interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

#### CONTACT

- **L** +91 8590 057 736
- in linkedin.com/in/pavithracaz
- Calicut, Kerala

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### 22 JUNE 2023 - 30 March 2024

# UI/UX DESIGNER & UI DEVELOPER

#### **Mentegoz Technologies Calicut**

- UI Designing Using Figma, Photoshop and Illustrator.
- UI Development using WordPress.
- Gained Teaching skills in UI/UX design and UI Development.

#### 26 JULY 2022 - 03 MARCH 2023

#### WEB DESIGNER

# Pixbit Solutions Private Limited Govt. Cyberpark Calicut

- Coded Sravana website using Tailwind
  - https://sravanahearingaidcentre.com/
- Revamped Global Branding website using Bootstrap.
  - https://globalbrandings.com/
- Redesigned Cakiyo Website.
- Worked on Kilban website using Tailwind CSS.
- Worked on Pixbit Website using Bootstrap.
- https://pixbitsolutions.com/

#### 16 MAY 2022 - 25 JULY 2022

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# Limenzy Technologies Pvt Ltd Govt. Cyberpark Calicut

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery Training.
- Hubspot Development Training.

#### 16 JANUARY 2022 - 17 APRIL 2022

# FULL STACK PYTHON DEVELOPER-Internship

#### **Baabtra Hilite Business Park Calicut**

- Frontend Development-HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax Training.
- Backend Development-Python, Django, PostgreSQL, JSON, API, Git Training.

# **SOFT SKILL**

- Creativity
- Problem Solving
- Analytical Skill
- Project Management
- Attention to detail
- Communication
- Adaptability
- Time Management
- Collaboration
- Work Ethic
- Quick Learner
- Multitasker

### **HARD SKILL**

- FIGMA
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- HTML
- CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- WordPress
- React
- Python
- Django
- PostgreSQL
- Adobe Premiere Pro

# **EDUCATION**

#### 2018-2021

#### **BCOM-FINANCE**

CALICUT UNIVERSITY

#### 2016-2017

# DIPLOMA IN DIGITAL IMADING

GOVT.ITI.MALIKKADAVU

#### 2014-2016

# **PLUS TWO-SCIENCE**

GAGHSS.CHALAPPURAM

#### 2014

#### **SSLC**

**GVHSS.MEENCHANDA** 

# **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Malayalam
- Tamil
- Hindi

# **HOBBIES**

- Reading
- Dancing
- Singing
- Drawing
- Vlogging